shareswift.com 2017-05-10

# ShareSwift - EgyszerЕ± mГіdja, hogy megosszd az ГЎllomГЎnyaidat

### ShareSwift Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the ShareSwift™ website located at www.ShareSwift.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of ShareSwift and its affiliated companies ("ShareSwift™", "we" or "us"). This ShareSwift™ Website Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") covers our treatment of Personal Information (as defined hereinbelow) and other information that we collect when you: (a) access or use the Site; (b) become a Member; and/or (c) use the Services. It is important that visitors are fully informed about the use of their Personal Information. We believe in 100% permission-based marketing. Capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning set forth in the ShareSwift™ Website Terms and Conditions ("Terms and Conditions"). 

**What Personal Information Do We Collect from You?**

ShareSwift collects only the data that is needed to open and manage your account. This data will not be used for any other purpose. ShareSwift takes every affordable precaution to protect your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction by taking all administrative, technical, and physical measures. We at ShareSwift.com respect your privacy. All information collected at ShareSwift.com is kept confidential and will not be sold, resued, or rented in any way. We do not share your infromation with any 3rd parties. 

**How We Use Personal Information** IP Addresses IP addresses are logged by ShareSwift.com to ensure account safety features availability, measuring usage and statistics. Email Addresses We collect email addresses of users at the time of registration as means of contact and verification. ShareSwift.com does not rent, sell, or share your emails with anyone. Disclosures of Exceptional Kind We at ShareSwift.com may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information suggests to actual act of violence or threatened harm or potential threats to the physical safety of any person or persons. Disclosure may also be required by law or if we receive a legal notice or similar request from authorities. Cookies ShareSwift.com uses cookies to store the preferences of users, only if they so choose. Third-Party Cookies The third-party advertisers we might have may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. Third-Party Advertising We use third-party advertising companies. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites for statistical purposes. 

**Other Websites**

The Site may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites. ShareSwift™ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be able to make a purchase through one of their third-party websites. In these instances, you may be required to provide certain information, such as a credit card number, to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and ShareSwift™ has no responsibility or liability relating to them. 

**Removal of Your Information/Opting Out**

At your request, we will provide you with a list of your Personal Information that we have in our database and, if you request, remove Personal Information that you have provided to us. You may do so by e-mailing us at privacy@ShareSwift.com. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may continue to contact you for the purpose of communicating information relating to your request for Services, as well as to respond to any inquiry or request made by you. To opt-out of receiving Services-related and inquiry response-related messages from ShareSwift™, you must cease requesting Services and cease submitting inquiries to ShareSwift™, as applicable Please note that deleting your Personal Information, or otherwise opting-out of receipt of communications from us or third parties, will only change or delete the data in our database for purposes of transacting future business on the Site and for managing future communications from us and third parties. These deletions will not change or delete Personal Information already collected as part of a particular transaction in our database, which may have already been shared with third parties, all as provided above in this Privacy Policy. You will need to contact third parties who may contact you directly to change your preferences or your Personal Information that they may be using to contact you. We provide users with the option to opt-out from receiving information sent via electronic mailings on behalf of third party advertisers. Users may unsubscribe from receiving e-mail at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every e-mailing. Unsubscribe requests can only be processed if you have registered with us in the first instance. If you have not registered with us and wish to opt out of receiving e-mail from a particular sender, please review that sender's opt out policy or contact that sender. Information sent via e-mail is prepared several days in advance, so users may continue to receive e-mail from us for up to ten (10) days following the unsubscribe procedures detailed above. If, after that point, a user is still receiving e-mail from us, the user should contact us at privacy@ShareSwift.com. 

The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy**

By using this Site and/or Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site; provided, however, that if at any point we decide to use personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify the affected Site users by way of an e-mail communication and provide them with the opportunity to opt-out of such uses in that e-mail communication. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site, Services and/or acceptance of our e-mail following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes and agree to continue receiving e-mail from us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please unsubscribe by Clicking Here. 

**Filing a Complaint with the Federal Trade Commission**

To file a complaint regarding our privacy practices, please Click [Here](https://www.ftccomplaintassistant.gov/FTC_Wizard.aspx?Lang=en). 

**Contacting Us about Privacy Questions or Concerns**

We value your privacy so if you have any problems with these Policy, please [Contact Us](http://shareswift.com/contact.html).
